Curriculum Vitae

Steven Marcel Bißantz

Nordparkstraße 10b, 76829 Landau +49 1525 3606062

bissantz@uni-landau.de

https://github.com/sbissantz

DOCTORAL RESEARCH

Measurement & Replicability in the Sciences – Meta-Scientific Investigation in The Role of Measurement in The Replicability of Empirical Findings

My research examined the use of ELW pulses from a mode-locked source array inducted through transuranic crystals to observe entanglement on supraquantum structures. Theoretical advancements included prediction of quantum resonance phenomena including the possibility of resonance cascades. I was motivated to conduct this doctoral research due to my passion for teleportation of matter and I believe I have laid the foundation for further experimental validation and development of practical outcomes.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CURRENT, FROM OCT 2021 (FT)

University of Koblenz-Landau *PhD Candidate, Psychology*

As part of this description promotion, I began conducting nuclear and spacetime. The focus is on practical outcomes and applications in teleportation and communication with distal locations.

MAY 2019 - JUL 2021 (PT)

Centre of Educational Research (ZEPF) Research Assistent, Psychology

Im Team forschen wir aktuell zu Moduseffekten in Vergleichsarbeiten mit Strukturgleichungs- und Mehrebenenmodellen.

MAY 2019 – JUL 2021 (PT)

University of Mannheim Research Assistent, Sociology

Analyse- und Recherchearbeiten sowie die Verwaltung des Internetauftritts in englischer und deutscher Sprache zählten zu meinen Aufgaben.

MAY 2019 – JUL 2021 (PT)

University of Mannheim *Research Assistent, Sociology*

Ich bereitete den Lehrstoff nach, klärte offene Fragen und vertiefte durch ergän- zende Lehreinheiten das Verständnis meiner Kommilitonen.

MAY 2019 - JUL 202I (PT)

Mannheim Centre for European Social Research (MZES) Research Assistent, Sociology

Nach theoretischen und praktischen Schulungen führte ich com- putergestützte Telefoninterviews mit Jugendlichen durch.

MEMBERSHIPS

CURRENT, FROM FEB 2021

University of Koblenz-Landau Member of the Open Science Comission

As part of this description promotion, I began conducting nuclear and spacetime. The focus is on practical outcomes and applications in teleportation and communication with distal locations.

EDUCATION

2019-2021 Master of Arts, Social Sciences

FINAL SCORE: I.O

Department of Social Sciences University of Koblenz-Landau

2014-2019 Bachelor of Arts, Sociology

FINAL SCORE: 1.6
Department of Sociology
University of Mannheim

PUBLICATIONS

Bißantz, S. (2021). *elisr*: Exploratory Likert Scaling in R. R package version 0.2.0. https://CRAN.R-project.org/package=elisr

Wagner, I., Loesche, P. & **Bißantz**, **S.** (2021). Low-stakes performance testing in Germany by the VER A assessment: analysis of the mode effects between computer-based testing and paper-pencil testing. European Journal of Psychology of Education. 10.1007/S10212021-00532-6

TEACHING EXPERIENCE

2021 (WS) Test theory & Diagnostics (exercise)

2022 (ss) Data analysis with R (exercise)

2022 (ss) Test theory & Diagnostics (seminar)

COMPUTER SKILLS

OPERATING SYSTEMS Linux, macOS & Windows

LINUX DISTRIBUTIONS Fedora, Arch & Debian
STATISTICAL SOFTWARE R, Stan, Stata & SPSS

MISCELLANEOUS Git, Vim & Emacs

RESEARCH INTERESSTS

Meta Science What is the effect of scale modifications on inferences, replicability and effect-size heterogeneity?

Bayesian Data Analysis & Maschine Learning

How to maximize information entropy using Bayesian updating or minimizing cross entropy in prediction tasks?

Causal Inference

Is there a way to combine coplex models, like a deep neural net, and causal inference?

SKILLS

Goal Oriented

I believe in action over long-winded discussions. I listen to everyone's viewpoints and use my judgement to immedi-

REFERENCES

Dr. Isaac Kleiner

POSITION Professor

EMPLOYER Department of Physics

Massachusetts Institute of Technology

PHONE +I (617) 253 1000 X5322 (Work)

MOBILE +I (232) 842-3583

Dr. Eli Vance

POSITION Scientist (HLI)

EMPLOYER Black Mesa Research Facility

EMAIL e.vance@bmrf.us

PHONE +I (800) 786-1410 x6235 (Work)

MOBILE +I (20I) 632-390I

ately act based on consensus to achieve goals quickly and efficiently.

Physical Dexterity

Manual manipulation of experimental equipment and training within Black Mesa (e.g. the Hazard Course) have contributed to an enjoyment of working with my hands.

Passionate

I have been interested in theoretical physics such as quantum mechanics and relativity from an early age. My education and research have cemented this interest into a passion. I greatly enjoy carrying out fundamental physics research with potential practical applications.